since reaches our climax.
Luffy...
I won't let you take a single member of my crew,
even if it kills me!
Epic Heated Combat, the fateful final conclusion.
He's back on his feet yet again!
What a guy!
He may fall,
but he gets right back up every time!
Why can't you just stay down?
You'll kill yourself!
Luffy!
He's battered and bruised!
He's tired and out of breath!
Epic!
He still stays tall!
With a glimmer in his eye!
All for the sake of his friends!
Now this is a daily fact mine!
I don't know how to say it!
I'm so periodic and secret!
Luffy!
We love you!
I'm gonna cry!
You're wrong, Luffy!
You can do it!
Luffy!
The crowd has spoken!
The crowd has touched our hearts!
No one has ever lasted this long against our boss!
No one has ever shown so much courage!
You idiots!
Jeez!
Don't you realize you're chilling for the enemy?
Come on, boss!
Boss!
You wait!
I'll end this soon!
Slow, slow, slow, slow, slow!
You'll have to do better than that!
Help!
Oh no!
He can't dodge!
His poor legs are too worn out to run!
It's too cruel!
I can't stand the watch!
Here!
Let me put you to rest!
Slow, slow, slow, slow, slow!
Boss goes on the offensive!
He slowed down the cannonball, but to what end?
Flying Foxy Fighter!
Watch out for my flied fist!
They're gonna knock you out at the speed of a cannonball!
He's using the Flying Foxy Fighter to finish his foe!
It may be slow now, but once the beam wears off, there's no escape!
Listen!
He used this beam on you a few seconds before you go!
I can't stand the watch!
Here!
Let me put you to rest!
I can't stand the watch out for my flied fist!
They're gonna knock you out at the speed of a cannonball!
He's using the Flying Foxy Fighter to finish his foe!
It may be slow now, but once the beam wears off, there's no escape!
Listen!
He used this beam on you a few seconds before the ball!
Dodge as soon as you're back to normal!
I can move!
Oh!
Straw Hat recovers!
But is it too late?
Nice try!
But I'm too fast!
Ah!
Watch out!
That thing's about to blow!
Here you go!
A parting gift!
A direct hit!
Ow!
I don't think Straw Hat will be getting up from that one!
Oh no!
Blue Bay!
That jerk!
Is he trying to kill him?
Is he trying to kill him?!
Back up!
No!
нос stout!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
But how?
You're going down.
Is that so?
And how do you plan to beat me
if you can't even stand up straight?
But never mind.
If that's how you want it,
then I'll just have to pound your face in
until you stay down for good!
Magneton! Nine tails!
Come, come, come!
Rush!
That's it!
Such intensity!
The fighters are unleashing a flurry of fists
at lightning speed!
Go!
Slaughter that box!
You can do it!
So fast!
So strong!
So brutal!
Slow, slow!
Slow!
Wait!
What?
He stopped moving!
Slow!
I...
I think Straw Hat is beat!
Wait! No wait! He's on his knees, but he's still moving, unlike our boss who's standing, but strangely frozen in place!
How did he...
Oh no, boss!
It's a mirror! A piece of mirror has fallen from Straw Hat's hand!
It was stuck in my afro. I got it when I broke the mirror.
Come come!
Noooooooooooo!
Ohh!
Boss, no!
Huh. Eight seconds.
Huh?
Could this be... the end?
Seven seconds.
Till what?
Six?
Say it ain't so!
Five!
Hey! Come on, you guys! Don't just sit there! Count along with me!
Four!
All right! We're almost at the end! Everyone together now!
Three!
Two!
One!
Three!
Two!
One!
Three!
Two!
One!
Three!
Two!
One!
Three!
Two!
One!
Three!
Two!
Four!
One!
Two!
Four!
One!
Ah! He's flying!
Up goes our boss! High into the sky!
Oh no, boss, come back!
Hooray! Hooray! Hooray!
Hooray! Hooray!
And now he finally comes down!
Captain! Captain!
Outside the battlefield!
Ladies and gentlemen, the final round of the daily back fight has come to an end!
After an epic battle between Captains, our boss's legendary record of 920 wins and zero losses has been broken!
I won't let you take a single member of my crew!
Even if they killed me!
Let's hear it for strong!
Help you me!
We did it! Stop!
Stop!
Stop! That's Elmo!
Our boss really lost!
We've seen it all today, folks!
Hey!
Don't just sit there, guys!
The boss needs our help!
Let's do something!
You can count me in!
Let's go!
The end of an hour!
You must need it!
Help me too!
The daily back giant has been toppled!
And the boy with the tiny crew and the massive afro has seized the day in a grand fashion!
You little show-off!
Who do you think you are?
Take this!
And this!
He's not bad!
He's really hurt!
You'll poke him to death!
Yeah, afro power my butt!
That was a close call if I've ever seen one!
Whoa, hey!
Let's not disrespect the afro here!
Look!
He's waking up!
Where are you?
He's not bad!
He's really hurt!
You'll poke him to death!
Yeah, afro power my butt!
That was a close call if I've ever seen one!
Whoa, hey!
Let's not disrespect the afro here!
Look!
He's not bad!
He's really hurt!
You'll poke him to death!
Yeah, afro power my butt!
That was a close call if I've ever seen one!
Whoa, hey!
Let's not disrespect the afro here!
Look!
He's waking up!
Where am I?
What happened?
Is it over?
Did I win?
That wasn't just a dream, was it?
Was it?
You don't need to freak out.
You beat him.
What a relief.
Everyone else said you'd lose, but not me.
You're a bad liar.
Guess it would've been a real pain if you'd lost.
Imagine being stuck on a boat with Foxy.
Screw that.
Boss, wait!
You gotta take it easy!
Hey, rubber boy!
I was pretty attached to that wind streak of mine!
I'm not pleased about you ruining it!
Boss, no!
I'm kidding, brother!
Let's shake!
What a man!
He's the best!
You're too kind, boss!
Hi-ya!
Take my shoulder through the sky!
Oh, no!
This guy's a real piece of work.
You forget the rules already?
Come on!
You got 500 new crewmates to choose!
He's right!
We haven't made the final exchange yet!
Chopper!
Robin!
I'm so happy!
Thank you!
Here, your mask.
You can have it back now.
Strahd starts out with two obvious choices!
The question is, who's next?
Don't leave us hanging!
Guess I'll take your flag!
You monster!
You'd strip my poor crew of their livelihood without a second thought!
I don't need your sail!
You gotta use that to go places, after all!
You hear that?
We're safe!
That's nice and all, but I'm afraid it's not that easy!
We have a flag on our sail, too!
We don't need your pity!
You want fair and square, so take it!
I got a plan!
I don't actually have to take the sail off the boat as long as I can take the mark off the sail!
And I can do that with paint!
Once you have a new flag, you should be fine, right?
Thank you, Strahd!
Your kindness is...
There!
It sucks!
Aw, you guys don't have to bow to me!
We're not!
Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hold on a second!
You still have another 497 crew members to pick!
You don't need any more!
The rules are the rules!
I don't care if you need them or not!
You're gonna pick those crewmates right now!
Do I have to?
Of course you do!
Stop complaining!
Hey, Luffy!
What?
Hey Luffy!
A crew follows their captain's orders no matter what, remember?
Hm?
Yes!
Good point.
That makes it easy!
Huh?
Hmm...
Easy?
What is?
I got it!
No problem!
Now, let's see...
You!
Me?
Really?
Yep!
And everyone from you...
Hmm...
To you!
Me?
How many people is that?
We have 500 total.
So excluding our boss, Hamburg and Porcha,
that should leave us with...
Oh, that's 497 exactly!
Well, there you go, it's settled!
Captain Loopy!
Nice, thanks!
Well, folks, this is Eco Movie Zoo
signing up for today!
And signing on is the Straw Hat's brand new MC!
Hey, cheers for the new Straw Hat Pirates!
I hate to say this, but no matter how you look at it,
the Mary can't hold this many people.
Ah, it's no big deal.
We'll just follow along in the Sexy Foxy
till we work something out.
Good point!
He'll do no such thing!
The Sexy Foxy is my ship, you miserable eggbrake!
Your ship, eh?
I'd like to see the three of them
run that huge ship by themselves.
They wouldn't last a week!
Yeah, fat chance!
Fat chance.
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop!
Ah!
Then go, you jerks!
Who needs you?
So long, X-Boss!
Don't catch a cold!
Wash your teeth twice a day!
Take a bath!
Hey, rubber boy!
Hm?
I'll make you pay for this!
Just wait!
That's supposed to be a joke, right?
Okay!
Listen, men!
It's time for your first job as members
of the new Straw Hat Pirate Crew!
Are you guys ready?
Yeah!
You can count on us!
Yeah, rubber boss!
You're all dismissed!
You mean you're kicking us off?
Yep, you got it.
Captain's orders are absolute,
so I don't want to hear anyone complaining.
I don't care if you join your own crews again
or if you go back to Splithead,
but whatever you do,
you can't stay with us.
So long!
Come back!
X-Boss!
We miss you!
We belong with the Foxy Pirates after all!
Well, that worked out nicely.
Hee-hee!
That's right, Shelly.
It's finally over.
Don't be afraid, girl.
The bad guys are gone.
I'm sorry.
I know what you're thinking,
but I won't ride on stilts ever again.
We'll catch up to the village, too.
I don't care how many years it takes us.
Huh?
You made it back!
We brought you a souvenir.
You're hurt.
Are you all right?
Huh?
Aw, this?
It's nothing.
Huh.
Thank you for your help.
Hee-hee!
Is that why you accepted the fight?
Because you wanted to help him?
And here I thought you were just being stupid again.
Man, you're rude.
What?
What's happening?
Guys, I don't like this.
It's huge!
What is that?
I might ask you the same question.
Whoa!
You mean that thing can talk?
I'm not a thing!
I'm a mole!
Mole, you say?
I don't get it.
I'M THE CHAMPION!
You dig?
Great.
Another weirdo.
Champion of what?
You really need to ask?
Great. Another weirdo.
Champion of what?
You really need to ask?
Obviously, I'm the world champion of hole digging.
As crazy as it sounds,
I'm challenging my own record as we speak.
That's no excuse for wrecking the old stilts guy's house.
Where is he supposed to live?
Huh?
What old stilts guy?
They call us a mole.
You like him?
Listen, Li Tanto,
I'm about to go for the world record in stilts standing.
Huh?
It won't be easy, so I may be up there for a few days.
But at least you'll have the mole to keep you company.
You can manage while I'm gone, right?
Uh-huh. I'll wait as long as I have to.
But you better come back a champion, okay, Grandpa?
You bet I will. Don't you worry.
I promise I'll make you proud.
It can't be.
It's really you?
Well, of course.
Grandpa!
Li Tanto!
I missed you so much.
I was so lonely without you.
You turned into a fine young man.
I'm so sorry I didn't get to watch you grow up.
I didn't mean to worry you.
I hope you can forgive me.
I didn't see that one coming.
When I thought about how hard my Grandpa was working on his world record,
it inspired me to start on a record of my own.
And suddenly, before I knew it,
all my loneliness turned into a passion for hole digging.
And now you're the champ.
Yup! I'm gonna dig through the whole world!
You ain't big, huh?
Just like the old stilts guy.
Yeah.
That's not a compliment.
Say, couldn't you follow one of your holes to reach the other villagers?
Huh?
Looks like it all worked out, huh?
Yes. I don't know how to thank you for all you've done.
Don't worry about it.
Thanks a lot, ma'am!
If you hadn't said something,
I probably would have been waiting for years to see the other villagers.
Farewell, my friends.
I won't forget you.
Again, thank you so much.
Take care on your way home, old man!
You too!
Wherever you may go, I pray for your safe journey.
That's that.
Time to head off.
Nami, is the log ready yet?
Sure is.
We're all good to go.
All right.
It's about time.
Yeah.
So what now?
Are we gonna snag ourselves a shipwright?
Yeah!
Just hold on, Mary!
We'll find a shipwright to fix you up in no time!
Yeah!
Have a nice.
Was it lost? Stolen? Who are you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!